javascript closures are functions that can access values outside of their own
javascript 闭包是可以访问它们自己的花括号之外的值的函数，
curly braces in order to call a function in your code the javascript interpreter
以便在代码中调用函数 javascript 解释器
needs to know about the function itself and any other data from the surrounding
需要了解函数本身以及
environment that it depends on everything needs to be neatly closed up
它所依赖的周围环境中的任何其他数据需要整齐
into a box before it can be fed into the machine
在被输入机器之前封闭成一个盒子
take for example a pure function that only depends on its own arguments and
，例如一个纯函数，它只依赖于它自己的参数和
internal data what we have here is a fully
内部数据我们这里有一个完全
self-contained closed expression when it's called it gets pushed onto the
独立的封闭表达式，当它被调用时它被推送到
call stack where it's executed and its internal data is only kept in memory
调用中 执行它的堆栈，其内部数据仅保留在内存中，
until it's popped back off the call stack but what if that function
直到它从调用堆栈中弹出，但是如果该函数
references data outside of its own scope like from the
引用其自身范围之外的数据，例如来自
global environment or an outer function that leaves us with an open expression
全局环境或外部函数，这给我们留下了一个开放的表达式
that references other free variables throughout the
environment now in order for the interpreter to call this function
现在在整个环境中引用其他自由变量，以便解释器调用此函数
and also know the value of these free variables it creates a closure to store
并知道值 在这些自由变量中，它创建了一个闭包，将
them in a place in memory where they can be accessed later
它们存储在内存中的某个位置，以后可以访问它们，
that area of memory is called the heap and unlike the call stack which is
该内存区域称为堆，与短暂的调用堆栈不同，
short-lived it can keep data in memory indefinitely
它可以将数据无限期地保存在内存中，
then decide once you get rid of it later with the garbage collector
然后再决定一次 您稍后使用垃圾收集器将其删除，
so a closure is not just a function it's a function combined with its outer state
因此闭包不仅仅是一个函数，它是一个与其外部状态或词法环境相结合的函数，
or lexical environment as you might imagine closures require more memory and
因为您可能会想象闭包比纯函数需要更多的内存和
processing power than a pure function but you'll come across many practical
处理能力，但您会遇到
reasons to use them the most important one being data
使用它们的许多实际原因最重要的一个是数据
encapsulation to prevent leaking or exposing data where it's not needed we
封装以防止在不需要的地方泄漏或暴露数据我们
can create a closure by defining an outer function that contains the state
可以通过定义包含状态的外部函数
then an inner function that operates on it the data contained here will not leak
然后对其进行操作的内部函数来创建闭包这里包含的数据将 不
out to the surrounding environment the inner function has access to data
泄漏到周围环境内部函数可以访问
defined in the outer function scope but the outer function does not have
外部函数范围中定义的数据，但外部函数没有
access to the inner function in addition many javascript apis are callback based
访问内部函数此外，许多 javascript api 都是基于回调的，
you can use closures to create a function factory that takes an argument
您可以使用闭包创建一个函数工厂，该函数工厂接受一个参数，
then returns a brand new function which can then be passed along to other
然后返回一个全新的函数，然后可以将其传递给其他
functions that expect a callback this has been javascript closures in 100
期望回调的函数，这就是 javascript 闭包 在 100
seconds but stay tuned because today we're going beyond 100
秒内，但请继续关注，因为今天我们将超过 100
seconds to take a look at one of the most famous javascript trick questions
秒来看看最著名的 javascript 技巧问题之一
that will wreck you on an interview if you don't know closures but first make
，如果你不知道闭包，它会在面试中破坏你，但首先要
sure to like and subscribe i'm trying to fulfill my childhood dream of getting to
确保喜欢并订阅 我正在努力实现我儿时的梦想，即获得
a million subscribers but it's going to be really hard to get there
一百万订阅者，但
if you don't click the button just kidding i have a ton of fun making these
如果你不点击按钮开个
videos and learn something new every time
玩笑，那将很难实现
a great example of which is this tricky javascript interview question the
一个很好的例子就是这个棘手的javascript 面试问题
question itself is what does this code log out let's go
问题本身就是这段代码注销了什么 让
through it line by line first we're declaring a variable i with
我们逐行浏览它首先我们声明一个变量 i
the var keyword then a for loop that will run three
使用 var 关键字，然后一个 for 循环将
times by incrementing that variable now inside the for loop is where
通过在 for 循环中增加该变量来运行 3 次，这是
closures come into play we define a function
闭包发挥作用的地方 我们定义了一个函数
log that console logs the global variable i
日志，控制台记录全局变量 i
this is not a pure function because it depends on a variable outside of its
这不是一个纯函数，因为它取决于 在其范围之外的变量上
scope therefore creating a closure then from
因此创建一个闭包然后从
there we set up a timeout and pass the log function as the
那里我们设置一个超时并将日志函数作为
callback this queues up a task to execute the log function after 100
回调传递这排队一个任务以在 100 毫秒后执行日志函数
milliseconds so what do you think the output of this
所以你认为这段代码的输出如何
code will be we're capturing the i variable in the closure for each
将是我们为循环的每次迭代捕获闭包中的 i 变量，
iteration of the loop so it would seem like it should log out
因此它看起来应该注销
as 0 1 2. but if we log it out it actually console
为 0 1 2。但是如果我们将其注销，它实际上控制台
logs three three times to understand why that happens we also
记录了三三次以了解为什么会发生这种情况 我们还
need to understand the difference between
需要了解
var and let when you use var in a for loop
var 和 let 之间的区别，当您在 for 循环中使用 var 时，
that variable actually gets hoisted up into the parent scope which in this case
该变量实际上会被提升到父作用域中，在这种情况
would be the global scope watch what happens when we change the variable to
下，它是全局作用域。当我们更改变量以
let we get our original expectation of a
让我们获得对
console log of 0 1 2. with var we have a global variable
控制台日志 0 12 的原始期望时，就会发生这种情况。使用 var 我们有一个全局变量
that we're mutating over and over again but with let we're creating a variable
，我们一遍又一遍地改变它，但是使用 let 我们创建了一个作用域的变量
that is scoped to the for loop in other words
对于 for 循环，换句话说，
it's local to the for loop and can't be accessed outside of it now remember
它是 for 循环的本地，并且不能在它之外访问现在
a closure is the combination of a function and its lexical environment
记住闭包是函数及其词法环境
in the case of let the closure is capturing the log function
的组合，如果让闭包捕获 log 函数
along with the variable i for each iteration of the loop which would be 0 1
以及 循环的每次迭代的变量 i将是 0 1
2. if we didn't have a closure here javascript would allocate that i
2. 如果我们在这里没有闭包，javascript 会
variable in memory in the call stack and then immediately
在调用堆栈的内存中分配 i 变量，然后立即
release it but because we do have a closure
释放它，但是因为我们确实有一个闭包
it stores that variable in the heap memory so it can be referenced again
将该变量存储在堆内存中，以便将来
when that closure is called by the timeout in the future
在超时调用该闭包时可以再次引用它，
but when var is used it's capturing the reference to the global variable
但是当使用 var 时，它会捕获对全局变量的引用，
the reason it logs three three times is because the timeout
它记录三三次的原因是因为
doesn't run until 100 milliseconds later long after that for loop has completed
timeout 直到 100 毫秒后才运行，直到for 循环完成
and iterated up to three we can actually
并迭代最多三个之后，如果您尝试在浏览器中运行此代码，我们实际上可以
examine this behavior in the browser dev tools by adding a debugger to the
通过在闭包中添加调试器来检查浏览器开发工具中的这种行为
closure if you try to run this code in the
browser with the devtools open it will take you to the sources tab and
devtools 打开它会将您带到源选项卡并
allow you to inspect the call stack and scope of the function
允许您在使用前导时检查函数的调用堆栈和范围，
when lead is used you can see we have a block scoped variable named i
您可以看到我们有一个名为 i 的块范围变量，
but when var is used that variable is now in the global scope
但是当使用 var 时，该变量现在位于 全局范围
which changes the way it's captured by the closure that's a pretty tricky one
，它改变了闭包捕获它的方式，这是一个非常棘手的
but javascript interviewers love to ask questions like this if you ever find
问题，但是如果你发现自己遇到这样的问题，javascript 面试官
yourself faced with a question like this the best thing you can do is talk
喜欢问这样的问题，你能做的最好的事情就是
through the code slowly and explain how a closure works
慢慢地讨论代码并解释关闭是如何工作的，
so they know you're on the right track even if you don't come to the right
所以即使你没有得出正确的
conclusion i'm going to go ahead and wrap things up
结论，他们也知道你走在正确的轨道上
there thanks for watching and i will see you
in the next one
在下一个